http://www.intrawest.com/privacy

Intrawest Privacy Policy
Intrawest is committed to the privacy of our customers and guests (“you” and “your”). The Intrawest Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to Personal Information that Intrawest collects, whether online, in person, through our call centers or otherwise.
“Personal Information” is information about an identifiable individual. Personal Information does not include information about a business or aggregated information that cannot be associated with a specific individual.
“Intrawest”, “we”, “us” or “our” refers to Intrawest Resorts Holdings, Inc., its subsidiaries and certain of its affiliates. Intrawest has an international presence and maintains offices and facilities in multiple jurisdictions throughout the United States and Canada. Except in circumstances where the privacy policy of an affiliate or partner applies, all of Intrawest’s business operations are subject to this policy.
This Policy does not apply to information about Intrawest’s employees or to information that is not Personal Information.
PERSONAL INFORMATION INTRAWEST COLLECTS AND HOW IT IS USED
Intrawest collects Personal Information in a number of circumstances during the course of operating our mountain resort adventure and real estate business.  We use this information in order to provide you with the best possible service and to meet our reasonable business needs.
We collect your personal information when you purchase a product or service or enroll in a program
When you purchase a product or service, make a reservation or enroll in a program, we collect personal information in order to process the transaction and administer the program.  We may also send you information relating to your purchase, reservation or program.  For example, if you make a reservation at one of our resort locations, we may send you information about the activities, events or offers taking place at that resort.  The information we may collect and use for these purposes includes but is not limited to:
your name and contact information to identify and communicate with you
medical information, such as allergies or medical conditions that we need to be aware if you are participating in lessons or other programs, or have dietary restrictions
payment card information to process transactions
age and/or birth date, gender and biometric data (such as height, weight) where this information is necessary in connection with the product, service, program or activity that you have requested (for example, we may need gender, height and weight to provide you with appropriate rental equipment)
photograph to identify you as a guest
whether you’re the parent or guardian of a minor guest
information about your preferences (such as preferred lodging room type).
In some cases you may provide us with personal information relating to a family member or other individual.  By providing us with personal information relating to an individual other than yourself, you represent that you have their consent to provide us with their personal information for the purposes described in this Policy.
When you submit an inquiry or provide feedback
We may collect your name, contact information and comments or questions when you submit an inquiry or comment, complete a survey or otherwise provide us with feedback about our business.  We may use this information to respond to your question and to improve our business, products, services and programs.
When you participate in a marketing initiative or create an online account
If you choose to create an online account profile, we may collect your name, contact information, age, gender, birth date, personal image, username and password and other information that you choose to provide (such as your preferences).
We may also collect your name, contact information, age and/or date of birth if you decide to participate in a marketing initiative such as a contest, sweepstakes or other promotion.  In some cases we may also ask you specific questions about your preferences or for feedback on our business, products, services and programs.  We use this information to administer the promotion, including contacting and announcing winners (where applicable), to improve our business, products, services and programs, and for marketing initiatives depending on your marketing preferences.
When you call our call center or we call you
We may record calls into and out of our call centers for the purposes of maintaining accurate records and for quality assurance and training purposes.  We will retain call recordings for as long as reasonably necessary for these purposes.
We collect your personal information when you visit our resorts and use Intrawest pass products and tickets
When you purchase or use Intrawest pass products and tickets, we may collect information regarding your geographic location, activities and purchases while you are at Intrawest resorts.  Intrawest pass products and tickets use either handheld scanner or RFID (radio frequency identification) technology.  Through the use of this technology, Intrawest may be able to collect information regarding your location at the resort, including the lifts that you ride, and depending on whether you have a payment card linked to your pass product, other commercial transactions that you complete at an Intrawest retail or restaurant location. We use this information to understand how our guests use our resorts and to understand your personal preferences.  Depending on your marketing preferences, we may also use this information to send you personalized offers and invitations.
Depending on your marketing preferences, we may also use this information to send you offers, invitations or promotions relating to our locations, products, services or programs that we believe may be of interest to you.  For example, we may monitor your commercial transactions or browsing habits on our websites or at our resort locations which may influence the personalized special offers and promotions that we send to you.
Several of our resorts use GPS tracking technology in connection with their ski and ride school programs in order to track and locate students on the mountain.  The GPS tracking technology is owned and operated by a third party service provider which may be provided certain information to operate websites on which you and/or your family members can track your day on the mountain.
At certain of our resort locations we may use video surveillance for the safety and security of our guests, employees and property. We will retain video recordings for as long as reasonably necessary for these purposes.
We collect your personal information from third parties
If you are a resident of the U.S., Intrawest may also supplement the Personal Information that you provide to us with information that we obtain from third parties.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION THROUGH COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
When you visit an Intrawest website, your web browser sends us certain information depending on the web browser that you use and your security settings.  This information may include your IP address, the name and version of your operating system, the name and version of your web browser, other technical data information, whether you accessed our website from a computer, mobile device or tablet, when you open emails we send you, the date, time, and duration of your visit, and geolocation data.  This Web browser data helps with system administration, traffic reposting, and auditing. It also helps us better understand who our guests are, how they use our services, and what we can do to improve the user experience. We may use this information to offer you products and services and to create aggregate statistics. This helps us improve your experience both online and at our resorts.
Intrawest also uses “cookies” to customize your website user experience by tailoring online content to align with your browsing habits. Cookies are small pieces of data, stored on your hard drive that send us information about your online browsing habits, including login and browsing history, button impressions, and personal preferences. Intrawest may also work with third party advertising networks that use cookies and similar technologies to track your use of our website and other websites so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your inferred interests. This advertising may appear on our website or on other websites. If you tell an Intrawest website to “Remember Me” or save your preferences, this information is stored using a cookie.  Cookies also tell us under which account a user is logged in to one of our websites and this information helps us protect your information by making sure your personal preferences are only displayed when you are actually logged in. Some cookies are also required to support the functionality of your transaction (e.g. putting items in your shopping cart).
We may use third party services, such as Google Analytics and Facebook, to provide us with information on how users interact with the content on our websites.  We may also allow social plug-ins with third parties, such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and Pinterest.  When you visit a webpage that contains a social plug-in, your web browser sends information to that social plug-in.  The third party plug-in sends content directly to your web browser which enables it to gain information that you have accessed a page on one of our websites. Intrawest does not collect Personal Information from a third party’s use of social plug-ins on our websites.  For information regarding the third party’s use of social plug-ins and how it may impact your privacy, you should refer to the third party’s privacy policy.
A Web Beacon is a tiny graphic with a unique identifier which is placed in the code of a Web page. Intrawest uses Web Beacons to count visitors to its websites and to monitor the traffic patterns within and between our websites, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to understand how you have come to our site, and to improve site performance. Web Beacons help us to measure the effectiveness of our content and other offerings.
You can choose to disable cookies using your web browser’s preferences menu. By turning off cookies, we will still be able to track your browsing history during a single visit to one of our websites however, we will not be able to link your browsing history during each of these visits to you, as you will be considered a new visitor each time you visit one of our websites.  Web Beacons will no longer be able to track your activity on our websites however, the Web Beacon may be able to continue to track activity based on your IP address.  Be aware that turning off cookies may disable certain functions on the website and cause it not to function properly or fully.   If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information online as described in this Policy, do not use our websites.
Intrawest may include links to third party sites on our websites.  When you click on those third party links, you leave the Intrawest website.  This Policy does not apply to third party sites or any information that you provide on those sites.
INTRAWEST MAY COMBINE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Intrawest may combine the Personal Information that you provide, or that we collect, in order to better understand your needs, requirements, and personal preferences so that we may improve our business, products, services and programs and optimize your experience when you visit our resort locations, or when you are dealing with an Intrawest team member, a call center representative, an Intrawest agent or other authorized third party.
Depending on your marketing preferences, we may also use this information to send you offers, invitations or promotions relating to our locations, products, services or programs that we believe may be of interest to you.  For example, we may monitor your commercial transactions or browsing habits on our websites or at our resort locations which may influence the personalized special offers and promotions that we send to you.
WHEN INTRAWEST SHARES PERSONAL INFORMATION
Intrawest does not sell your Personal Information. Intrawest may, however, share your Personal Information with third parties in the following circumstances.
Service Providers – we may share  your personal information with third party service providers (including affiliates acting in this capacity) who provide services on our behalf such as payment card processors, call center, web-site hosting, data management, identity verification (for example, in order to confirm your eligibility for special offers, such as military discounts), market analyses, marketing, advertising, and contest administration, or your personal information may be collected by such service providers on our behalf.
Partners - Intrawest may disclose your Personal Information to third-party partners in situations where the disclosure is necessary in order to complete or provide the service, product, or information that you have purchased or requested.  For example, Intrawest may disclose your Personal Information to a third-party tour operator if you purchased a tour from the third-party tour operator using one of our resort’s websites.
Other Entities in the Intrawest Group of Companies – Personal Information relating to Intrawest customers is maintained in a single database that is accessible to the Intrawest group companies.  This means that Personal Information collected by one Intrawest company may be accessible by other entities or businesses within the Intrawest group of companies.  The purpose of this sharing is to facilitate customer bookings and reservations across all Intrawest location(s) and, depending on your marketing preferences, allow all Intrawest group companies to understand your preferences and send you information about their locations, products, services and programs.
Corporate Transactions – Intrawest may disclose your Personal Information to another entity, if necessary, in the event of an actual or proposed merger, sale, a re-organization including as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings, or for the purposes of evaluating and/or performing such transaction.
Special Circumstances – Intrawest may consider it necessary or may be required by law to disclose your Personal Information with our attorneys, or with others who are legally authorized in certain emergencies where the health, safety, or well-being of a person is at imminent risk, or if required in order to comply with a court order, or as otherwise required to comply with the law.
CONSENT
Intrawest collects, uses and discloses your Personal Information as outlined in this Policy and with your consent, except where permitted or required otherwise by law. We may be required or permitted under statute or regulation to collect, use or disclose Personal Information without your consent, for example to comply with a court order, to collect a debt owed to us or if there is an imminent threat to an individual’s health, safety, or well-being.
Your consent may be express (for example, oral, written, or electronic) or your consent may be reasonably inferred or implied from something that you do (for example, use of our websites, implies consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as described in this Policy). In some instances, an authorized representative may consent on your behalf. In the case of minor children, a parent or legal guardian may consent to our collection, use and disclosure of a minor’s Personal Information.
You may withdraw your consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restraints. However, your withdrawal of consent might affect your experience and Intrawest’s ability to provide products or services to you, or quick and accurate service to you either on-line or through our service agents.
HOW TO MANAGE YOUR MARKETING PREFERENCES
If you no longer want Intrawest to use your personal information for marketing purposes, including to send you promotional communications, you may contact us (see “Contact Us” section below) and ask to be removed from our mailing and/or contact lists. We may ask you for more information where required in order to identify you correctly.
You may also manage your email subscriptions by clicking on “Unsubscribe” to stop receiving future promotional communications from us, or by clicking on “Manage My Email Preferences” found at the bottom of any of our emails you receive in order to manage your email subscriptions.
Children Under 13: Intrawest does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen, without prior consent of the child’s parent or legal guardian. Intrawest’s websites and social media pages available online are not directed to users under the age of thirteen. If you believe that your child under the age of thirteen may have provided Intrawest with Personal Information online please contact us at yourprivacy@intrawest.com and Intrawest will take appropriate action.
ACCESS AND CORRECTION
Request A Copy: To obtain access to, or a copy of, your Personal Information that we have on file for little or no cost contact yourprivacy@intrawest.com or send a written request to 1621 18th St., Suite 300, Denver, CO 80202 Attention: Chief Privacy Officer. Access to this information may be denied if you are unable to verify that you are the subject of the request. Information may also not be provided when giving you access to the information would threaten someone’s life or security, reveal third-party Personal Information, breach confidentiality, violate attorney/solicitor-client privilege, disrupt a formal dispute resolution, or impede a law enforcement investigation.
Accuracy: We endeavor to ensure that your Personal Information is as accurate, complete, and as up to date as necessary for the purposes for which it will be used or shared. If you would like to request correction of your Personal Information that we have on file you may write to us at yourprivacy@intrawest.com or 1621 18th St., Suite 300, Denver, CO 80202 Attention: Chief Privacy Officer.
HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION
We will generally keep your Personal Information on file for a reasonable period of time in order to meet our needs as described herein and as applicable, the needs of the parties to whom we disclose it. This file will be maintained on our servers or those of our service providers and will be accessible by our authorized employees, service providers and representatives.  We maintain reasonable and systematic controls, schedules, and practices to retain and destroy Personal Information.
Internal Protections: Intrawest protects Personal Information by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. We have policies and practices to protect against loss, theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, modification, or destruction. While we make efforts to protect your information we are not in a position to guarantee that your Personal Information will always be secure. There may be factors beyond Intrawest’s control which may result in loss or theft, or unauthorized access, use or disclosure of your Personal Information. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representation on non-disclosure of your Personal Information. We also employ a Chief Privacy Officer to be accountable for Intrawest’s compliance with these policies and whom you may contact at the address below with any question, concern or complaint.
External Protections: To protect information disclosed to service providers, Intrawest uses contractual or other means to provide a similar level of protection so that service providers treat the information confidentiality, implement appropriate security measures and only use and disclose the information for the purposes of providing the applicable services.
Please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored and processed by Intrawest and its affiliates and service providers in Canada and the United States where Intrawest, or its affiliates or service providers operate and maintain data. While outside of Canada, your Personal Information will be subject to applicable foreign laws, which may permit foreign government, regulatory or national security authorities to have access to your Personal Information in certain circumstances.  By providing us with your information, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Policy.
Responsibility
Intrawest’s Chief Privacy Officer is responsible and accountable for Intrawest’s compliance with this Policy and will handle all inquiries and complaints.
Contact Us: If you have any questions, you may contact us at:
Mail:            Intrawest
1621 18th Street, Suite 300
Denver, CO 80202
Attention:  Chief Privacy Officer
Phone:         1-877-477-6777 (North American Toll-Free)
1-303-749-8218 (Local and International)
Email:          yourprivacy@intrawest.com
SUBJECT TO CHANGE
This Policy is subject to change, and may be supplemented or modified at any time. You should check this site regularly to stay up-to-date about changes to this Policy. If material changes are made, we will notify you by placing prominent notice on our website www.intrawest.com/privacy.aspx.
California Customers:
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 entitles California customers to request information concerning whether a business has disclosed Personal Information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As stated in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell your Personal Information. California customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this law or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies may contact the Chief Privacy Officer at the address above.
Contact Us
Careers
UPDATED Privacy Policy
Politique de confidentialité actualisée
Terms of Use
Code of Business Conduct & Ethics
code d'éthique
Anti-Corruption Policy
